[mic feedback]
[host] Congratulations to everyone
who survived the first Main Match.
We will now begin the first Seeker Vote.
-Seeker?
-[Jieun] What?
-Seeker Vote?
[Horseking] It turns out
there's a Seeker. [gasps]
[Eunsil] What's going on?
[host] The Seeker is a hidden architect
who creates chaos and controls
the course of the chase,
secretly working
to prevent the players from winning.
[scoffs]
Someone has been fooling us.
[host] Before the Seeker Vote,
we have an announcement.
In yesterday's Main Match,
"Cops and Robbers,"
the Seeker's mission...
SEEKER'S MISSION
SUCCESS
...was completed successfully.
[chuckles nervously]
[ZZONE] It was so shocking.
I had no idea at all.
-[host] By completing their mission...
-I just got chills.
...the Seeker will gain a special benefit.
[Jimin] I was completely caught off guard.
[Ddolddol] I realized the Seeker
was already steering the game in a way
to give themselves the upper hand.
THE SEEKER WAS AMONG THEM YESTERDAY
[Jieun] I realized
you can't trust anyone now.
Are they trying to sabotage
their own team?
-I think so.
-"Prevent the players from winning."
[sighs] I hate games
where you have to think.
-It's you, isn't it?
-No, no, no.
[host] Excluding Gyeong Sujin,
the Seeker is someone
among the 12 players.
Then, the Seeker could be
among the eliminated players too.
They could be here or over there.
THE SEEKER COULD BE IN PRISON
Starting now, prison visits are allowed,
and players in prison
can vote as well.
If the Seeker is successfully caught,
the Seeker will immediately become
an elimination candidate.
However, if you fail to catch the Seeker,
the player with the most Seeker Votes
and the player chosen by the Seeker
will go to the Death Match
through an Elimination Vote.
The Seeker Vote will start
in an hour from now.
-[Ddolddol] Starting now?
-[Jieun] Now?
[Joonsu] Right away?
[ZZONE] So this is why
it's called Deadly Tag.
SEEKER VOTE
This is intense.
[Ddolddol] If the Seeker picks me,
I'm at a disadvantage.
And if I get falsely accused
of being the Seeker,
I'm still in a bad spot.
[Junseo] I don't know who it is,
but I feel like I'm being toyed with.
I'm worried that this will affect
people with preconceptions,
and they'll automatically think,
"A spy? Park Jimin must be the one."
It was giving me such a headache.
[Pani Bottle] I think their quest
was definitely designed
-to make their team lose.
-Right.
Otherwise, nothing would benefit them.
PLAYERS IN PRISON GUESS SEEKER'S MISSION
-Make their team lose...
-Yeah.
-...and not to go to prison.
-And they survive.
Maybe that's their mission.
Then, if we narrow it down,
it's not the cops.
-It's not the cops.
-Yeah, it's not a cop.
I don't think it's Jimin or Jieun.
It's not us either.
-Right, because we're here.
-Yeah.
It's not us either.
If the Seeker fails,
does this mean their mission
gets revealed before the vote?
Then, they must've not revealed it
because they were successful yesterday.
[ZZONE] Yeah, I think you're right.
If they failed,
the mission would've been revealed today,
but they succeeded yesterday.
If we vote now,
-it would just be on hunches.
-[Jaegyun] Exactly.
-Pretty much.
-Yeah.
No way.
[Eunsil] I don't think we can choose now.
We had no idea
what the Seeker's mission was.
We had no proof or hunches.
And no one really seemed suspicious.
[Jaegyun] Honestly, I have no idea.
So from that point on,
I talked with people more.
PLAYERS VISIT THE PRISON
-Did you hear about the Seeker?
-We did.
We discussed and concluded
that the Seeker's role was clearly
to make their team lose
and avoid getting voted out.
-That was our guess.
-Their mission.
So, the Seeker lost?
It doesn't matter to them
if their team wins or loses.
That's irrelevant to them.
[Pani Bottle] We were thinking the Seeker
-wasn't a cop.
-It's not a cop.
[Pani Bottle] Why?
Because all the cops won.
The people in prison are guessing
the Seeker is not among the cops
because the cops
all worked together and won.
I don't really understand
why Pani Bottle and Yang Dail
-came to that conclusion.
-Right.
[Ddolddol] If they were a cop,
they would've done their mission
-without the others knowing.
-That's possible.
[Ddolddol] It may not be about
winning or losing.
Maybe the mission was
to put together your team as you want
and win the game.
-That could be true.
-[Jimin] If that's the case...
-So, we can't rule out the cops.
-[Jieun] You're right.
What makes me think
the Seeker could be a cop is,
Eunsil was the Narcotics cop,
and the three of us were Drug Criminals.
It would be easier for a female cop
to handle the other women.
[ZZONE] That does seem pretty fishy.
Maybe they chose people
who would be easier to control.
This keeps bothering me.
"A hidden architect who creates chaos"
and "prevents the players from winning."
Exactly. Look, as an architect,
they can plan things out.
Then, they might have formed
the cops team.
Exactly.
[Jaegyun] I can't stop thinking
about the word "architect."
Whatever the mission was,
there's no way such strong players
would've all been selected as cops.
[dealer] Please point to one card
of your choice.
DRUG CRIMINAL, ASSAULT CRIMINAL, BURGLAR
CI, VIOLENT CRIMES, NARCOTICS
Please point to one card of your choice.
-This one.
-Is this the card?
CRIMINALS NEVER HAD ANY COP CARDS TO PICK
Please point to one card of your choice.
COPS COULD NEVER BECOME CRIMINALS
[host] The Seeker's Mission
will now be revealed.
According to the rules of Deadly Tag,
you have been selected as the Seeker.
[dealer] Please choose
one key number from 1 to 14.
PLAYERS EACH CHOSE A DIFFERENT KEY
UPON RECEIVING FUNDS
[♪ mysterious music playing]
[host] In the Main Match,
"Cops and Robbers,"
your mission is
to make the three cops win.
Select three players
who will play the role of cops.
MAKE THE THREE COPS WIN
SELECT THREE PLAYERS TO BE COPS
[dealer] Put the three player cards
in the envelope.
CLOSE TO THE SEEKER'S MISSION OBJECTIVE
The odds were pretty high
that I'd become a cop,
because there were seven cards left.
I just wish I knew who was before me.
-[ZZONE] The order?
-[Horseking] Yes.
You were likely after me.
Kim Ddolddol. Then, Horseking,
So you picked that when you went in?
I was the first one to go in,
and I got Good Citizen.
And then, I picked Good Citizen
right after that.
You're right. Two Good Citizens in a row.
[dealer] Mr. Kim Ddolddol.
Mr. Horseking.
You are a Good Citizen.
TWO GOOD CITIZENS IN A ROW
AT THE START BY CHANCE
[Horseking] According to the odds,
it doesn't make sense.
The dealer told me to only choose
and said he'd flip the card.
That's when I started thinking
that they could all be the same cards.
If you look at it that way,
ruling out the cops doesn't make sense.
[ZZONE] You have a point.
That cop team was
-just too strong.
-[ZZONE] It was ridiculous.
[Horseking] It was as if pieces
of a puzzle were falling into place.
THE SEEKER IS A COP?
If the architect is one of the cops,
they've done their job
because the cops won.
I'm just going to say what I think.
If I dare to speak my mind,
I have a feeling it's Sanghyun.
DDOLDDOL SUSPECTS SANGHYUN
First of all, I felt he woke up
way too early today.
-Where are you going?
-[Sanghyun] I'm going on a walk.
CLUE 1
SOLO WALK AT DAWN
[Ddolddol] Maybe he tried
to explore the area?
His vibe today is different
from how it was yesterday.
Also, we found out about the Seeker today.
-He was unfazed.
-[Ddolddol] But he wasn't surprised.
[host] We will now begin
the first Seeker Vote.
[Ddolddol] You know how people
have gut feelings? It's just my hunch.
-All we can do is guess right now.
-[Ddolddol] Yes, that's right.
So, I think it could be Sanghyun.
[Jimin] Kim Ddolddol
was pretty convincing.
So more and more people
started to suspect Sanghyun.
That's fine too.
As long as I don't get eliminated.
SANGHYUN TALKS WITH A COP
What do you think?
I had some suspicions
-about Kim Ddolddol.
-[Sanghyun] I see.
[Eunsil] Or maybe Horseking?
How did Ddolddol contact you?
-He only sent you intel.
-By phone.
-Yes, he messaged me directly.
-By phone?
We got nothing from him.
It's because he's handsome.
-Is that why?
-[all laughing]
He could be his type.
Am I unattractive?
No, I mean, he could be his type.
[Junseo] I don't know. It's just a hunch.
I'm being cautious about saying this.
It's just the impression
I get from people.
But the Seeker has to...
SANGHYUN ENTERS DINING ROOM
[Jieun] Right, right.
Right, right.
[♪ tense music playing]
[Jieun sighs]
[Sanghyun] You know how something
just feels off about someone?
I'm curious. Is there only one Seeker?
Yes, one.
Does it say that anywhere?
I don't see it written anywhere.
That's a new take.
THERE COULD BE TWO SEEKERS?
I'm just thinking there could be two.
SANGHYUN THROWS OUT HIS THEORY AND LEAVES
That's a new angle.
-Two Seekers.
-[Ddolddol] Right.
That's when I was completely convinced
that it was Sanghyun.
We only had to catch one person.
It felt like he was trying to distract us,
so I headed straight to prison.
When the cops came here,
-did they say there might be two Seekers?
-No.
[Ddolddol] Well, they just told us.
-They didn't tell us.
-[Ddolddol] Sanghyun did.
In that case, it would split the votes.
[Joonsu] A distraction tactic?
DDOLDDOL SUSPECTS SANGHYUN
When Ddolddol said that,
I thought, "He's right."
Sanghyun is the one
I'm most suspicious of.
Kim Ddolddol
seems to have really good instincts.
Do we have to vote within an hour?
That wasn't mentioned.
Earlier, I talked with Jaegyun
and Horseking here.
They seem to be
really suspicious of the cop team.
They're suspicious of the cop team?
[Jimin] Yes, because the Seeker
planned the whole game.
But I feel like it can't be the cops.
The reason why I thought
there could be two Seekers is
Ddolddol...
Sorry.
-[Jimin] What? What did you say?
-Mr. Ddolddol and Joonsu
kept talking to each other.
When we visited the prison earlier,
I went to get food,
and they were talking separately.
Everyone was at prison,
but what did they need
to talk about in that situation?
DDOLDDOL & JOONSU TALK PRIVATELY
If there are two Seekers,
it could be those two.
That's what I thought.
But wouldn't that be unlikely,
considering how Ddolddol
betrayed Joonsu yesterday?
-Who knows? Maybe to win alone...
-But that could be part of his plan.
[Eunsil] Right, maybe the mission
was to sabotage his team.
[Sanghyun] I didn't know
that other people
were suspecting the cops though.
[Jaegyun] Very shady.
EXCEPT FOR SANGHYUN,
ALL MALE PLAYERS HAVE VISITED THE PRISON
-[Joonsu] It's warm.
-[Jaegyun] It's warm as hell.
[Joonsu sighs]
[♪ contemplative music playing]
Do you guys think
the Seeker is among the cops?
[Sanghyun] Hmm.
Do you think the Seeker
is a cop too, Jaegyun?
I do have that suspicion.
To me, this feels like nothing
but a witch hunt,
because the game
would become too easy then.
The more we talk about it,
the more confusing it gets.
[chuckles]
[Horseking] I can't decide.
-[Jaegyun] I have no idea.
-I really can't pick.
[Sanghyun] I don't know what happened,
but Ddolddol must've been very persuasive.
It felt like everyone wanted me out.
Why is everyone doing this to me?
15 MINUTES BEFORE SEEKER VOTE
[Ddolddol] There wasn't much time left.
If I didn't do something,
it felt like the votes would be split.
[ZZONE] Who is it?
[Ddolddol] Are the ladies all here?
[Jimin] Yes, you can come in.
[Ddolddol] I thought people who would be
easily swayed were there.
I needed to play politics
to get their votes.
So, here's the thing.
If Sanghyun is the Seeker,
we made the right choice for survival.
But if he's not the Seeker,
we'd feel bad,
and no one would vote him out.
The one the Seeker picked
should be eliminated.
FOUR PEOPLE SWAYED BY KIM DDOLDDOL
We have nothing to lose, right?
-It's the most reasonable choice.
-It is the most reasonable.
He's the biggest threat,
so why would we keep him around?
Here's 80 million won
-in personal funds.
-Thank you.
REMOVE A WEALTHY RIVAL
-He's one step ahead.
-I know.
I think I got gaslit in that moment,
so I started thinking...
"Maybe it really is Youn Sanghyun."
Maybe it's the right move strategically.
[Ddolddol] The women
were all nodding there.
I thought, "Okay, I convinced them."
Then, I went to the room
where Jaegyun and Horseking were.
Listen, this is what
I just told the women.
-We need everyone on the same page.
-Right.
I spoke to him one-on-one just now
while looking at his eyes.
[Sanghyun] Do you think it's one person?
I'm guessing there's only one.
Starting with two
would make the game too complicated.
That's true.
Maybe I'm biased,
because I'm fixated on him.
But I got the feeling
he was kind of smirking.
Plus, he's an actor,
so he's the only one
who can stay composed and put up a front.
So, here's the thing.
If Sanghyun unfairly becomes
an elimination candidate,
people will vote
for someone else out of guilt.
Either way, Sanghyun survives.
Horseking and I were picked
first and second
-as Good Citizens.
-Right.
DDOLDDOL GATHERS VOTES
[mic feedback]
[host] We'll now begin the Seeker Vote.
Once you've made your decision,
please go to the Dealer Room
and cast your vote.
Hello.
[dealer] Please cast your vote
to identify the Seeker.
SEEKER VOTE
YOUN SANGHYUN
Sorry, Sanghyun.
[Jaegyun] Since
we've gathered enough votes...
[Horseking] We should vote for Sanghyun
since it gives us a majority.
-[shivering]
-[♪ contemplative music playing]
[Pani Bottle] Damn,
it's tough now that I'm here.
I'm sorry.
I gave it some thought
and voted for ZZONE.
SEEKER VOTE
ZZONE
PANI BOTTLE VOTED FOR ZZONE
Here's another option.
To survive the Death Match,
pick someone weaker.
That's the only option.
If you're not sure, pick ZZONE.
Yeah, vote for ZZONE. Help us out.
If you aren't sure, go with ZZONE
so we can survive the Death Match.
The Seeker will pick
a strong player for sure.
[Pani Bottle] Logically,
we should bring someone down
we might have a chance against.
We stopped looking for the Seeker.
I targeted ZZONE.
Let's be strategic and pick someone
we're most likely to beat.
SANGHYUN 3
DDOLDDOL, JAEGYUN, HORSEKING
ZZONE 3
PANI BOTTLE, SUJIN, DAIL
[host] The Seeker Vote has ended.
Please gather in the Main Hall.
[♪ tense music playing]
I guess someone's going to go down.
[mic feedback]
[host] We will reveal the results
of the Seeker Vote.
[Ddolddol] A lot of people
were swayed by me.
I felt like I'd convinced them.
[ZZONE] I think the people in prison
were determined to go after me.
[Eunsil] I decided to go
with the majority.
[Sanghyun] Since Ddolddol
started accusing me,
I thought people
would vote for me as the Seeker.
[host] The player
who received the most votes is...
Kim Ddolddol.
I didn't expect that result at all.
I was really shocked.
-[chuckles]
-[gasps]
[Ddolddol] Who on earth was it?
Was I stabbed in the back
by someone I trusted?
SILENCE FILLS THE MAIN HALL
[Sanghyun] If I'm in danger,
I might as well go after Ddolddol.
30 MINUTES AGO
[Jieun] Right after Ddolddol left,
Sanghyun walked in.
What are you going to do?
To be honest,
when the four of us were talking earlier,
your name did come up.
Ddolddol's name came up too.
Because yesterday, Ddolddol deceived us.
[Sanghyun] With Ddolddol targeting me,
it worked out in my favor.
I could use public opinion
and muddy the waters a bit.
When it came to the messages
Ddolddol sent me,
he was wrong about the part
that was causing confusion.
You mean the info he told you?
It wasn't entirely correct.
So, here's the thing.
He came all the way here
to create confusion.
Ddolddol lied the day before.
[host] Good Citizen.
DURING COPS AND ROBBERS
Kim Ddolddol.
KIM DDOLDDOL WAS THE TRAITOR
Let's compare the moment
when we got tricked and now.
Jieun said they felt similar.
I agree with voting out Ddolddol
because he keeps doubting me.
-It should be him.
-Ddolddol?
-Okay.
-Ddolddol.
SETTLED ON DDOLDDOL
SEEKER VOTE
KIM DDOLDDOL
[chuckling]
[Sanghyun] I thought he was pretty smart,
but now I'm a bit disappointed.
[host] Also, here is the result
of the first Seeker Vote.
In terms of arresting the Seeker...
[Jieun] I wasn't completely sure,
but I thought Ddolddol
was the most suspicious one.
[Eunsil] I thought
he was trying to frame Sanghyun
because he was the actual Seeker.
[Sanghyun] I wasn't sure. I really wasn't.
[host] ...you have failed.
[Jimin] We're doomed.
[Ddolddol] How can they be that slow?
I was so pissed off.
I was 100% sure it was Sanghyun.
[Sanghyun] Why did he have to target me
when he wasn't even sure?
[ZZONE] I felt completely blindsided.
[Eunsil] I was totally stunned.
If it's not Kim Ddolddol,
we have to vote again.
[host] Lastly,
we will reveal the elimination candidate
chosen by the Seeker.
LAST NIGHT
The Seeker Room has opened.
DEADLY TAG
RULES
[distorted voice] The person
I'd like to eliminate is...
THE ELIMINATION CANDIDATE
CHOSEN BY THE SEEKER IN ADVANCE
[host] Between Kim Ddolddol
and the person chosen by the Seeker,
the one who receives the most votes
will become
the final elimination candidate.
If the person chosen by the Seeker
is Kim Ddolddol,
Kim Ddolddol
will automatically be confirmed
as the elimination candidate
without a vote.
The elimination candidate
chosen by the Seeker is...
[Horseking] I feel like
the Seeker will choose me.
[Jaegyun] What if it ends up being me?
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[host] The elimination candidate
chosen by the Seeker is...
Kim Ddolddol.
THE SEEKER PREDICTED
THE SEEKER VOTE RESULTS ACCURATELY
[♪ moody music playing]
[Ddolddol] Who's the Seeker?
I had to know who the Seeker was.
[host] Kim Ddolddol,
please leave the area immediately.
I really did my best.
-Well, it's not over yet.
-It's not over.
[sighs loudly]
I was sent straight to prison
without being an elimination candidate.
Why? Because it was
Kim Ddolddol versus Kim Ddolddol.
So I was the one who got the most votes
as the suspected Seeker.
On top of that, I was also the one
the Seeker wanted to eliminate.
Maybe I got too involved.
I kind of regret it.
THE MAIN HALL IS LEFT IN SHOCK
How could they both be the same person?
That's epic.
-[Sujin laughs] Someone's coming.
-Here he comes.
-[Sujin] My goodness!
-[Dail] Welcome!
-Mr. Ddolddol.
-[Pani Bottle] Excuse me.
Please get changed.
We have rules here too.
That's not the right attitude.
-Is there some strict hierarchy here?
-[Sujin laughing]
Hello, let me introduce myself.
What should I do first?
Maybe I should clean first.
-Want me to clean this up?
-[Sujin] No, it's fine.
I guess I'm the newbie here.
What can you do?
I better adjust quickly to prison life.
I have to survive.
I'll survive, get back out there,
and find out who the Seeker is for sure.
[♪ serious music playing]
3:00 A.M.
DEADLY TAG
RULES
[host] Seeker, please select
the next elimination candidate.
[distorted voice] It was a perfect play.
Ah. It was so thrilling.
[Eunsil sighs]
-[Eunsil] So now...
-[Junseo] Mmm.
Are you confused?
I think it's Sanghyun.
I hope I'm wrong,
but I also do feel that Sanghyun...
I'm suspicious of him.
What makes you think that?
Why do you suspect him?
They said there was a benefit
that could give the Seeker
an advantage right from the start.
I think maybe it was about
choosing a team.
You and I became cops.
Then, it was obvious
that cops would have a huge advantage.
I actually had my suspicions all along
in the back of my mind.
Can I ask who you voted for?
[Jaegyun] To be honest,
it was Youn Sanghyun.
-For real?
-[Jaegyun] Yes.
So we talked about it.
Ddolddol said if he was chosen
by the Seeker,
we should suspect Youn Sanghyun.
And the Seeker really picked Ddolddol,
so that's when I thought,
"Wait a minute."
[Pani Bottle] Who do you think
they'll vote for next?
[Ddolddol] I think they'll pick Sanghyun.
Wouldn't it be weird
not to suspect him at this point?
You openly accused Sanghyun,
and you ended up getting eliminated.
So naturally, Sanghyun should be
the one everyone votes for next.
SANGHYUN WILL LIKELY BE VOTED AS SEEKER
I'm 99% certain that it's Sanghyun.
[Pani Bottle] So no matter
who gets taken out among us,
let's vote for Sanghyun next round.
But if it's not him,
we're back to square one.
[Ddolddol] I think
we might build a bond this way.
[Pani Bottle] The problem is,
one of us has to be eliminated.
[Ddolddol] We developed a bond
we didn't have before.
We were determined to find a way back
and catch the Seeker no matter what.
Sanghyun,
you're not getting away with this.
[Jieun] Are you the Seeker?
It's not me.
I realized I couldn't continue like this,
so I decided to get aggressive.
Isn't this going exactly
how the Seeker wants?
-[Jimin] Yes.
-[Jieun] Exactly.
The person the Seeker chose
-got voted out anyway.
-[ZZONE] The same person...
Then, is it among the six of us
who went after Kim Ddolddol?
It's possible. The odds are--
Would it have been necessary
to target Kim Ddolddol
-as the Seeker?
-[Jieun] I thought about it.
[ZZONE] There is a possibility.
It might just be a coincidence.
[Sanghyun] When we happened
to accuse Kim Ddolddol,
-it's like, "This is perfect."
-[Jieun] Exactly.
-They may have thought that.
-[Jieun] Yeah, we don't know that.
[Sanghyun] When we started leaning toward
voting for Ddolddol,
Jimin did kind of take the lead.
If we all agree on one person to vote for,
that person will definitely be out.
Yeah, they'll definitely be out.
Then, how about we all vote
for the same person?
The best option we have
is actually voting for Ddolddol.
JIMIN GAVE IDEA TO VOTE FOR DDOLDDOL
He's the only one we can agree on.
Because who else can we pick?
Sanghyun, ZZONE, or Joonsu?
-Okay, then Ddolddol?
-[Sanghyun] Ddolddol?
I thought it worked out well.
Let's make this useful.
Maybe I should steer people
toward Jimin as the Seeker.
[sighs heavily]
This is so stressful.
[Junseo] Why?
I'm suspicious of two people.
[Junseo] Who?
[Sanghyun] Jimin and Jieun.
[Junseo] Jimin and Jieun?
Why?
[Sanghyun] There's something off
about them.
I feel like they're hiding something
when they talk.
Whenever we try to figure out
who the Seeker is, it feels like...
they stop halfway.
I don't know. It's just a gut feeling.
Horseking.
SANGHYUN GOES TO HORSEKING
-Who do you think it is?
-[Horseking] Who? I'm not sure.
My gut tells me it's Jieun or Jimin.
With Jimin, it's not just a hunch.
There are quite a few things
that made me suspicious of Jimin.
[Horseking] You think
she's playing politics?
Yeah, I believe she's just really good
at playing the game.
SANGHYUN STARTS TARGETING JIMIN
The one who was behind the idea
of going after Ddolddol
was actually Jimin.
And to be fair, I was part of that too.
I agreed to go with Ddolddol
because he'd been suspicious of me.
I thought I'd go after him as well.
[Horseking] So Jimin took the lead?
It was a group decision,
but she was the one who picked him.
The upside of going with Jimin is
that she's influential,
so it's worth looking into her.
[♪ suspicious music playing]
JIMIN IS UNAWARE OF SANGHYUN'S SCHEME
[Jimin] Sanghyun
seems so nervous right now,
which makes me think it might not be him.
I do feel bad for Kim Ddolddol.
I feel guilty,
so I keep thinking about it.
But honestly, I thought
the prison uniform looked pretty cool,
so I kind of wanted to try it on.
[Sujin] Blue.
[Sujin laughing]
-[Pani Bottle] It looks good on you.
-Hello, everyone.
[Pani Bottle] What are you in for?
-[Ddolddol] I was falsely accused.
-[Pani Bottle] "Falsely accused."
I have a cool undertone,
so blue looks great on me.
-It's mealtime.
-[Sujin] You can put it down there.
[Ddolddol] Everyone, the food is here.
-I'll bring it over for you.
-[Pani Bottle] You can leave it.
-[Sujin] Wait, the food...
-[Dail Kimchi and bean sprouts?
-What?
-[Pani Bottle] Did we get less food?
[Ddolddol] They gave us kimchi
and bean sprouts for our meal.
This is seriously bad.
I need to get out of the prison life fast.
I can't sleep with makeup on.
But I should just sleep.
Who cares about my skin?
-[Dail laughs]
-[Ddolddol] This is nice.
The sound of the water is like ASMR.
Am I made for prison life?
[Joonsu] What a nice day.
[♪ rock music playing]
[Sanghyun] What an interesting place.
[Jaegyun exclaims]
[Horseking] This place is scary.
-[ZZONE] Wow. Interesting.
-[Sanghyun] I know.
[ZZONE] This place is totally abandoned.
[Jieun] I should lure people over here.
This place is unbelievable.
[Junseo] There were a lot of structures.
The first thing I noticed was
how surprisingly spacious it felt.
[Joonsu] The doors were ripped off,
and the roof was covered in rust.
It was kind of scary.
[mic feedback]
[host] Welcome to the game area, everyone.
We will reveal
the second Main Match of Deadly Tag.
The second Main Match is...
"Time Between Dogs and Wolves."
"Time Between Dogs and Wolves"
is a nine-player game of cat and mouse
in which the roles of hunter and prey
switch as time goes on.
There is a total
of three roles in this game.
Dogs, Wolves, and Hunters.
Dogs can only tag other Dogs,
receiving one point per tag.
A player tagged by a Dog loses one point.
Wolves can tag Dogs or Wolves,
receiving three points per tag.
A player tagged by a Wolf
loses three points.
Hunters can tag Dogs or Wolves,
receiving two points per tag.
A player tagged by a Hunter
loses two points.
The roles will vary depending on
who they can or cannot tag.
If a player incorrectly tags
someone they're not allowed to,
they will lose two points.
So, Dogs and Wolves
can't tag Hunters, right?
No.
[Joonsu] They're basically
invincible then.
The Hunter is the best role.
[host] Before the game,
every player receives one Wolf marker
and one Hunter marker.
They must place these markers
on the six time slots
from Monday to Saturday.
If a Wolf marker is placed on a time slot,
the player becomes a Wolf.
A Hunter marker makes them a Hunter.
And if there is no marker,
they become a Dog.
Each day can have
a maximum of three players assigned.
But on Wednesday, there is no limit
on the number of players.
Should we all have a dogfight
with a Wolf on Wednesday?
I think I'd lose that fight,
so I won't mess around.
[host] Starting from the player
with the least amount of current funds,
players will enter in order
for the first round of placements.
The second round of placements
will be done in reverse order.
The chase will last 15 minutes
for each day,
and once the time runs out,
the game will automatically move on
to the next day.
At this point, players' roles
will not be revealed,
and only the number
of Wolves and Hunters will be revealed.
You don't know who's who,
so you can't just tag anyone.
If you tag the wrong person,
-you'll lose points.
-[ZZONE] Right.
Gosh, this is tricky.
[host] Any player with a score of
minus 20 points or lower during the game
will be immediately eliminated.
The game will consist of two rounds.
The player with the highest score
at the end will be the winner,
receiving 20 million won in personal funds
and one Elimination Immunity Pass.
On the other hand,
players with scores minus 20 or lower
will become elimination candidates.
They will choose two players
without Elimination Immunity Passes.
Along with one player
selected through an Elimination Vote,
they'll enter a Death Match.
I think it'll all come down
to where you're placed.
If you choose Hunter
and there are three Hunters,
it's over.
If you're the only Hunter,
you're invincible and can tag anyone.
You have to be careful.
It's a battle of wits.
[Jieun] I think good liars could have
an advantage.
[Joonsu] Even if I'm just a Dog,
if I act bold and approach a Hunter,
they might think I'm a Hunter
and get scared.
[ZZONE] I think the key
will be to psych people out.
[host] The chase area
consists of two zones,
the Residential Area
and the Factory Complex.
The Residential Area has open spaces,
making it easier to chase or run away.
The factory complex has
buildings and obstacles,
making it easy to hide or ambush others.
Next, here's how the tag system works.
At the start of the game,
each player gets one patch.
If you stick it on another player's back,
the tag is successful.
Sorry about that.
-You stick them on.
-[Joonsu] You tag them.
It'll be easier than ripping it off.
Yeah, it's much easier to stick them on.
[host] Also,
you cannot tag the same player
more than once on the same day.
You'll now have 30 minutes
for private discussions.
ROUND 1 PRIVATE TALKS
Does the Seeker still have
a mission during this too?
-We have to identify their mission, right?
-[Jaegyun] Yeah.
THE SEEKER STILL REMAINS A MYSTERY
Can an alliance even work here?
If someone lies within the alliance,
you're done for.
Exactly. The Seeker's role is
to sabotage the game
so no one ends up winning.
The Seeker's role could be big today.
Yeah, totally.
An alliance with the Seeker
will likely lead to losing,
because they'll prevent you from winning.
I think Sanghyun is my number one suspect
-as the Seeker.
-Yeah.
[Jaegyun laughs]
If you team up with him,
you'll be in big trouble today.
Then, vote me out.
-Seriously, just vote me out.
-I'll handle it. I got it.
-Why do you keep saying that? I get it.
-[Jieun] I'm testing you.
[Sanghyun] How many times will you say it?
Don't cry. Don't cry, don't cry.
[Sanghyun] She's been accusing me
as the Seeker since yesterday.
[Jieun] Are you the Seeker?
[Eunsil] I think it's Sanghyun.
It seems like it's Sanghyun.
UNDER SUSPICION SINCE LAST NIGHT
[Sanghyun] It felt like everyone
was suspicious of me.
So I felt kind of...
bitter and lonely.
I think I might play
on my own for this game.
No, if you team up,
you're guaranteed to win.
Team up? How?
For example, [whispers]
you'll have to lie a little.
Let's say I'm a Wolf on Friday,
but you tell everyone
that you think I'm a Dog.
[Jimin] I figured
if a Hunter reveals on their own
when they're playing,
I'd be able to figure things out.
So I made a proposal to Eunsil.
And I wanted to team up with Yuk Junseo.
Because his competitiveness,
speed, and stamina
would be very helpful to me.
So I wrote him a note.
TEAMING UP WILL GIVE US AN ADVANTAGE
LET'S WORK TOGETHER
Junseo, can you go
-ask for water?
-Sorry?
-Water? What water?
-Can you get some water?
-Drinking water.
-For drinking?
You go ask them since you look scary.
[laughing] She makes people
who look strong do errands.
Hey.
Where did he go?
Where is he?
PRETENDING TO SEARCH
You have to ask... Hey.
AND PASSES HIM THE NOTE
Could we get some water?
[Eunsil] What's your plan, Junseo?
Your offer was very nice,
but I'll go solo for now.
Since the Seeker has a mission
to create confusion,
I thought teaming up with others
could be risky.
[Jimin] I can't team up with Junseo then.
What do I do?
What about you?
We still don't have anything concrete.
I don't trust anyone enough
to share information either.
Of course, because you can't
show anything clearly.
There are conditions within the rules,
so I can't really trust anyone.
I thought about it over and over,
but I couldn't trust anyone.
I wasn't sure who I should team up with.
Everyone seemed suspicious.
Seriously,
this is so hard.
It's not easy.
Whenever I suggested teaming up,
everyone seemed as if they would be
the ones losing out.
But that's when I started thinking.
Maybe I should actually use
this situation to my advantage.
-[ZZONE] Joonsu.
-[Joonsu] Yes?
What are you going to do?
[in English] Ladies first.
-[in Korean] Well...
-[Joonsu] Did you decide to team up?
Team up? No. No one's teaming up.
Everyone's on their own.
Come over here.
So basically,
-we just need to avoid coming in last.
-[ZZONE] Right.
How about we don't tag each other?
-And no voting each other out.
-[ZZONE] Sounds good.
Then, should we go with that?
[ZZONE] To be honest,
anyone could easily tag me
because everyone's strong physically.
I needed to find someone to team up with.
-[Jieun] ZZONE.
-This won't do. I shouldn't try to fight.
-Can you not go after me?
-[ZZONE] Me?
Aren't you going to tag me?
Tag you? I'm not planning to.
-I'm scared.
-Me too. Same here.
It looked like Jieun and Joonsu
were thinking about forming an alliance.
It was actually an alliance
of the weakest.
-When you...
-[ZZONE] Let's have a chat.
When you're the Hunter,
if you tag her, you get three points.
-Wait, that's minus points.
-Wait, no.
-That's minus points.
-No.
There's three of us,
and we each get a day as a Hunter.
We won't know who else is a Hunter,
but we'll know one of us will be one.
The others won't know
which one is a Hunter.
If each of us takes a day,
one of us will be a Hunter half the time.
Then, Hunters...
[Joonsu] Since we're weaker players,
instead of putting all our Hunters
and Wolves on the same day,
we decided to spread them out.
One of us becomes a Wolf on Monday,
and another person becomes
a Hunter on Tuesday.
Our strategy was to protect each other.
If someone comes and tries to tag us,
since one of us is a Hunter,
the Hunter can stop them.
They don't know who it is,
so what can they do?
As a group of three,
we won't be alone. Do you get it?
Then, we won't have to hide as much.
[ZZONE] Looking back,
since we're the ones at the bottom,
we had less funds
and were the first ones
who could place our markers.
The remaining spots
were three sets of three,
so we were in a position to get
a rough idea of how they'd be placed.
I thought it could work in our favor.
I'll go with Saturday. [whispering]
ALLIANCE'S PLACEMENT PLAN
-I'll take Monday too.
-[Jieun] I'll do this day.
I'll do Monday.
-[Jieun] I'll take this one.
-It's the most risky one.
We'd be almost invincible.
Isn't this a guaranteed win?
It feels like
we have a pretty decent chance.
One of us might get in
the top tier in rankings.
[host] Round 1 marker placements
will begin now.
-[♪ exciting music playing]
-Jaegyun and Sanghyun.
HORSEKING
Do wolves usually have
different-colored eyes?
They're like Siberian Huskies.
It's heterochromia.
Different-colored eyes.
That's how they are when you look at them.
ROUND 1
MARKER PLACEMENT
Should I be a Hunter?
ZZONE GOES FIRST
Hunter, Wolf.
Hunter. Wolf.
[gasps]
PLACEMENT ROOM
Hello. [gasps]
MON, TUE, WED, THU, FRI, SAT
[dealer] Ms. ZZONE,
place your marker on the board.
I'll go with this.
You've placed
the Hunter marker on Saturday.
MARKER PLACEMENT RULE: ONLY ONE HUNTER
OR WOLF MARKER CAN BE PLACED AT A TIME
[Joonsu] This is scary.
LEE JOONSU IS SECOND
[dealer] Mr. Lee Joonsu,
place your marker on the board.
EARLIER PLACEMENTS ARE HIDDEN
I'll place the Hunter marker on Thursday.
You've placed
the Hunter marker on Thursday.
Ms. Shin Jieun,
place your marker on the board.
[Jieun] Really?
In that case...
[Joonsu] We agreed on the days
we'd each place our markers on,
but I was really worried
that Jieun might betray us.
I'll go with this.
[dealer] You've placed the Wolf marker
on Wednesday.
MARKER PLACEMENT CONTINUES
[host] Marker placement is complete.
[footsteps approaching]
[distorted voice] Am I...
meant to be the spy?
[dealer] We will designate the goal
for the Seeker mission.
Please name two players.
Shin Jieun
and Hwang Jaegyun.
I wonder how fun today's going to be.
THE SEEKER IS STILL ON THE MOVE
[host] Round 1's chase will begin shortly.
Please head to each of your positions.
-[♪ exciting music playing]
-It's so spacious. It's really big.
I need to figure out
my strategy for this area.
If there are one Hunter
and two Wolves,
that'd be the best.
[host] Once the marker placements
are revealed,
the round will begin.
[Jimin] There are two Wolves
and two Hunters?
[♪ contemplative music playing]
[Jaegyun] They said
there'd be three in total.
They clearly said
there'd be three in each slot.
[host] Each day can have
a maximum of three players assigned.
But on Wednesday, there is no limit
on the number of players.
I tried to place
my Hunter marker on Monday,
but I heard it was full.
MONDAY
[dealer] Monday already has
three markers in place,
so you cannot place another one.
But it showed two Wolves and two Hunters,
so I didn't understand what was going on.
I knew right away that something was off.
[alarm blaring]
[host] Monday has begun.
JANG EUNSIL
On Monday, my role was a Dog.
I took some tarp to make a tent...
and hid right from the start.
I wanted to peek through
and see who came by.
PARK JIMIN
I'm not someone
who can overpower others physically.
So I figured I'd better hide
and stay safe.
DEFENSIVE STRATEGIES FOR DOGS
YOUN SANGHYUN
It's a dead end.
[♪ exciting music playing]
SANGHYUN SEARCHES FOR PREY
JANG EUNSIL
I have to tag someone.
[Eunsil] That scared me.
MUYEONG FACTORY
[Sanghyun] Gosh, I'm beat.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
Where are they?
[Jimin] There were a lot of places
to hide there.
It was such a relief.
I decided to hold out a little longer.
[♪ rock music playing]
[Joonsu] ZZONE, come with me.
Let's go together.
[Joonsu] I met up with ZZONE as planned.
If someone comes and tries to tag us,
they don't know who it is,
so what can they do? Say, "Tag me."
Then, we won't have to hide as much.
THE ALLIES HIDE THEIR ROLES
ZZONE, LEE JOONSU
Hang on.
Hang on, hang on.
Someone's here.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
I'll cover your back.
I'll watch our backs.
It's Jaegyun.
THEY RUN INTO HWANG JAEGYUN
[ZZONE] We ended up running into Jaegyun
from the start.
He's the most athletic out of everyone.
SHIN JIEUN
[Jieun] On Monday, I was a Dog,
so I wanted to quickly reunite
with ZZONE and Joonsu.
RUNS INTO HORSEKING
-What are you?
-Me?
Of all people, the first person
I ran into was one of the strongest.
[Joonsu] What are you?
[Jaegyun laughs] Hey.
Are you a Hunter?
No.
Even if I'm a Dog, I should act fearless.
Then, they won't come after me,
because they'll mistake me
for a Wolf or Hunter.
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Jaegyun] Ah, so you two are Hunters.
JOONSU TAGS JAEGYUN
He came charging in confidently,
so I ran away
because I assumed he was a Wolf or Hunter.
-What are you?
-Me?
Are you a Hunter?
I am... a Hunter.
-You're a Hunter?
-Yes.
HORSEKING, SHIN JIEUN
They don't know if I'm a Dog,
a Wolf, or a Hunter.
I thought I should pretend to be a Hunter.
-What do you want?
-Hold on.
Wait, what are you? Are you a Hunter?
-What are you?
-What?
-I can't tell you.
-I told you mine.
-What are you doing?
HORSEKING IS THE REAL HUNTER
[Horseking] You're a Hunter?
JIEUN INSISTS SHE'S A HUNTER
You shouldn't come close then.
[Jieun] The funny thing is,
I was chasing Horseking
and he kept running away.
I felt like things were more in my favor
than I expected.
With this strategy, I think I can avoid
being in last place.
Hunter.
So Jieun is a Hunter.
A CONFUSED HUNTER
Jieun is a Hunter?
That doesn't add up.
[alarm blaring]
[host] Tuesday has begun.
[Jaegyun] You're dead meat, Joonsu.
HWANG JAEGYUN
I got tagged by Joonsu.
JOONSU TAGGED JAEGYUN ON MONDAY
I got you.
I needed to get that punk at least once.
SPOTS JOONSU
[panting]
I was a Dog that day.
but I ran to Jaegyun.
[Joonsu] Want to exchange information?
-What?
-[Joonsu] Want to share info?
-You tagged me.
-[Joonsu] I'll leave this here and talk.
You tagged me once.
Do you want to share information?
Want to catch the Seeker with me?
-What do you want?
-Leave it here?
Leave it there for now.
-I'm tossing it away.
-Okay.
Back up.
-What is it?
-Back up.
Do you have any information?
I'm a Hunter.
Right now?
LEE JOONSU, HWANG JAEGYUN
You're lying.
-I'm not. It's true.
-[Joonsu] You're not a Hunter.
Hey, you made the offer.
You put it on? Let's go.
-Why do you keep following me?
-[Joonsu] Sorry.
[Jaegyun] Hey, Joonsu tagged me twice.
Where's Joonsu?
Hey, Joonsu!
Where did he go?
-I have a patch on my back, right?
-No.
NO PATCH WAS TAGGED ON HIM
Joonsu, you're dead meat.
[Joonsu] I was still a Dog,
so I acted bold and confident again.
I was going to tag him,
but something felt different from earlier.
I felt something had changed.
I figured he wasn't a Dog,
so I walked up with my bare hands
and tapped him on the back.
I can be a bit sly.
I just couldn't believe it at all.
I got blindsided by a kid
who's not even 20 yet.
I felt so betrayed.
I can't believe Joonsu.
[panting]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
LEE JOONSU
[Jaegyun] Joonsu!
[Joonsu] ZZONE!
[Jaegyun] Geez, this punk's good
at running away!
Hey, hey!
[Jaegyun sighs]
JAEGYUN FAILS AGAIN TO GET REVENGE
-[alarm blaring]
-[host] Wednesday has begun.
[panting]
[Sanghyun] I was a Dog on Wednesday,
so I have to stay hidden for now.
YOUN SANGHYUN
HORSEKING TAGS JAEGYUN
JUNSEO TAGS JIEUN
The messages popped up on my phone.
I was really shocked.
Tags were happening so fast.
Things are crazy now.
It's a party.
HORSEKING
[Horseking] Once I became a Wolf
on Wednesday,
I wanted to tag every single one of them!
HORSEKING TAGS ZZONE
[host] Tag confirmed.
Go ahead and run if you can.
I'll tag you all.
YUK JUNSEO
[Junseo] I was a Hunter on Wednesday.
My goal was to tag
every single person I saw.
-[Jaegyun] Spare me just this once.
-[Junseo] What?
JAEGYUN'S LOST IN THE MAZE
-[Jaegyun] Spare me.
-[Junseo] Sorry.
[host] Tag confirmed.
JUNSEO TAGS JAEGYUN
Tag confirmed.
HORSEKING TAGS JIEUN
JUNSEO TAGS ZZONE
Tag confirmed.
-Sorry.
-It's okay.
What on earth?
Are these fools
just playing without thinking?
[host] Tag confirmed.
JUNSEO TAGS JOONSU
[dealer] Please retrieve your patches.
[Junseo] I'd tagged almost everyone,
and I was pretty exhausted.
SUPPLY STATION
[ZZONE] You can't do this.
[Horseking] There's no point
in tagging me.
[Jieun] How come?
Are you trying to tag first place?
Yes, I need to get more points.
[Horseking] That's...
[♪ intense music playing]
[Junseo] I spotted Horseking,
so I decided to tag him.
JUNSEO CHASES HORSEKING
[Junseo pants]
[Horseking] I'll never get caught.
DID I GET AWAY?
[sighs heavily] He's so relentless.
HORSEKING RUNS FOR HIS LIFE
JUNSEO KEEPS CHASING HORSEKING
[sighs]
It was scary when he was chasing me.
GIVES UP IN THE END
-Are you a Wolf?
-[Junseo] What?
[Horseking] Are you a Wolf?
JUNSEO TAGS HORSEKING
I'm out of breath.
This is too damn hard.
Geez.
I wanted to get away, but I was exhausted
"HE TAGGED MANY THAT DAY"
from all the running.
I couldn't keep going.
MUYEONG STORE
[Eunsil] I think Junseo is the top player.
[Joonsu] Really?
I keep getting alerts on my phone.
-For real?
-Yeah.
[Joonsu] You're right.
JUNSEO TAGS FIVE PLAYERS
-[Eunsil] So...
-[Joonsu] Why is he so good?
[Horseking] I'm so beat. [pants]
Junseo is totally out ahead.
I realized he had created a huge lead.
[sighs]
It didn't work out the way I planned.
I thought I had this game in the bag,
but I let my guard down.
YUK JUNSEO
[Jimin panting] Geez,
I'm so bad at running.
I can't handle this.
PARK JIMIN
NO TAGS
I had no idea what to do at that point.
My alliance plan didn't work out.
Your offer was very nice,
but I'll go solo for now.
I think I might play
on my own for this game.
[Jimin] I can't really run well.
I'm so exhausted.
INN
I realized this was a game
that put me at a disadvantage.
I had no idea
how I was going to get through this.
INCINERATOR
[exclaims]
JIMIN RUNS INTO JUNSEO
There's someone over there. Please.
JUNSEO TAGS JIMIN
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Junseo] Sorry.
[both panting heavily]
Could you please check my score?
MARKER PLACEMENT AND SCORES
CAN BE CHECKED HERE
Mr. Yuk Junseo, your score is six points.
[Junseo] Geez.
I tagged Jimin
but I lost points.
How did this happen?
I was really flustered.
Where is everyone?
GIGGLING
My strategy was to fake them out.
My plan was to get tagged
as much as I could when I was a Hunter.
[dealer] You've placed the Hunter marker
on Wednesday.
I figured there would be
a lot of reckless tagging in this game.
If that happened,
it would lead to a lot of negative points.
So, maybe the person
with the fewest negative points
could end up winning.
PARK JIMIN
[host] Tag confirmed.
SANGHYUN TAGS JIMIN
I was like,
"Please tag me, please tag me,"
so I kept taunting them.
I got tagged so many times.
No, hold on.
[host] Tag confirmed.
ZZONE TAGS JIMIN
[Jimin] What? Wait.
Wait, Joonsu.
[host] Tag confirmed.
JOONSU TAGS JIMIN
They'll end up losing points,
so my strategy paid off.
[alarm blaring]
[host] Thursday has begun.
I'm a Wolf on Friday though.
MUYEONG FACTORY
[Sanghyun] Jimin.
I need to talk to you.
From Monday to Thursday,
a total of nine people have been Wolves.
What are you talking about?
Check the text again.
Just once.
There have been nine Wolves, right?
CHECKING THE CHAT NOTIFYING ROLES
I've never been a Wolf yet,
but it already shows nine Wolves.
I analyzed how many Wolves
and Hunters had appeared.
I was trying to figure out
what Friday would be like
and prepare for the game.
But I got confused
when I realized
that there'd been nine wolves by Thursday.
-Three. Right.
-Three.
-Seven. Nine.
-Yes. Eight.
And mine is left.
JAEGYUN HASN'T BEEN A WOLF EITHER
But that's 10.
Each slot could only hold
three roles from the start.
-Right?
-[Jaegyun] Yeah.
Let's find out who played
as a Wolf on which day.
[Jieun] Let's look into it.
-[Jaegyun] After the first round.
-[Jieun] Okay.
[Junseo] What is going on?
The Wolf count was off.
I wondered why there were extra Wolves.
I was very suspicious.
[host] Friday has begun.
[Jieun screams]
[Eunsil] It's Friday,
so there isn't much time left.
[Jieun screams]
No!
EUNSIL TAGS JIEUN
-[host] Tag confirmed.
-Tagged.
YOUN SANGHYUN
I was a Wolf on Friday.
I needed to hurry up.
SANGHYUN TAGS JIEUN
[host] Tag confirmed.
[Jimin] I was a Dog on Friday,
so I had to hide.
[Junseo] I stayed hidden
almost the whole time.
JOONSU TAGS EUNSIL
-[host] Tag confirmed.
-[Joonsu] I got you.
[Jaegyun] Hey.
Hey!
Hey, Eunsil.
You can't use wrestling on me!
Wait, this is cheating.
MUYEONG TOWN HALL
PLACEMENT ROOM
[dealer] Hello, Ms. ZZONE.
-I'd like to check my score.
-[dealer] We will check Ms. ZZONE's score.
Your score is negative 19 points.
[gasps]
I actually got tagged so many times.
I was supposed to hide,
but I couldn't find a spot.
ZZONE WAS TARGETED BY PREDATORS
Wait.
One of the people
I had teamed up with was a Wolf.
JOONSU WAS A WOLF ON WEDNESDAY
[ZZONE yelps]
I have to tag them now.
JOONSU WAS A HUNTER ON THURSDAY
THEY WERE TARGETED AS A GROUP
Wait!
-[Eunsil] I got her.
-[ZZONE] Wait...
They tried to stay together with me
but I kept getting tagged.
That's when I lost a bunch of points.
PLOPS DOWN
I have no idea what to do.
Do I take the gamble or not?
I got minus 19 points.
I'm headed to the Death Match.
Seriously, I'm a candidate!
Seriously, I'm not lying!
Wait, I swear. Listen.
I'm going to the Death Match.
I got minus 19.
-What?
-[ZZONE] If I go under minus 20,
I'll head to the Death Match and pick you.
-[Eunsil] How can I trust you?
-Let's go now
-and check my score.
-[Eunsil] Are you sure?
-I'm not good at math.
-[ZZONE] Do the math. I swear.
Do the math.
Look at how many times I got tagged.
-I got tagged eight times.
-I'll believe you.
[ZZONE] I mean, I don't care,
but I'll go vote right away.
[Eunsil] Okay.
So that's why you were just sitting here.
I've got nothing to lose.
[ZZONE] I was in danger
of finishing dead last.
I decided to act bold and go,
"If I get tagged, then so be it."
I chose to push through with confidence.
[Sanghyun] Are you done?
I'm at minus 19, so if you tag me,
let's be elimination candidates.
-Is that so?
-Tag me, and I'll take you with me.
Not me. I'm absolutely rooting for you.
HANDSHAKE
-Hey, be careful.
-I'm always on your side.
Tag me.
He ran away from me.
This isn't as bad for me as I thought.
I'm at minus 19 points.
Then, can I tag you?
If you want to go to the Death Match,
be my guest.
[scoffs]
Then, I'll automatically vote for you.
RUNS OFF
-Me? Want to be up for elimination?
-I have no choice. No.
Seriously, I'll pick you.
I'll really pick you.
[Horseking] You've come to terms with it?
-Yes.
-Okay, embrace it. I'll give you that.
When will you be a Hunter?
-Saturday.
-[Jieun] Saturday?
-Okay. You'll give it a shot then?
-Yeah.
I need to give it a shot on Saturday.
PLANNING TO GO FOR IT ON SATURDAY
I was so anxious.
GNAWING ON HER PEN
I figured I just had to
hold out until Saturday
to turn things around.
I'll push through to the end.
[host] Saturday has begun.
ZZONE IS SATURDAY'S LONE HUNTER
There's no one here.
Let's check.
PARK JIMIN
[Jimin] I was a Wolf on Saturday,
but I laid low.
It's because my goal
was to avoid being last.
-And there's ZZONE.
-I'm at minus 19 points.
If you want to go to the Death Match,
be my guest.
ZZONE REVEALED SHE'S LAST
That's when I decided to stay hidden.
They managed to hide so well.
I couldn't find them anywhere.
They disappeared completely.
I'm going to the Death Match.
I got minus 19.
I'm really at minus 19 points.
WITH A LIKELY ELIMINATION CANDIDATE
THE PLAYERS GO INTO HIDING
I thought it was a good strategy,
but it turned out to be
a double-edged sword.
I felt so helpless and frustrated.
[Junseo] What are you doing?
-Oh. Junseo. [chuckles]
-What are you doing?
-I'll tag you.
-[Sanghyun] I missed you.
-Why? Are you a Hunter?
-No.
[Sanghyun] No tagging this time.
How does that sound?
Deal?
I won't tag you.
-I ran so much. Since yesterday.
-[Sanghyun] How long have you been here?
Since yesterday?
That's a long time.
[Jieun] You need to tag just anyone.
I need to tag someone.
I kept running around,
but I couldn't find anyone at all.
[alarm blaring]
[sighs, grunts]
I felt terrible.
[host] Round 1 is over.
Before moving on to Round 2,
we will announce the current rankings.
In third place,
Youn Sanghyun.
In second place,
Yuk Junseo.
-Who's first place?
-[host] In first place,
Horseking.
1ST HORSEKING
2ND JUNSEO, 3RD SANGHYUN
8TH ZZONE, JIEUN
Junseo.
In terms of tags,
don't you have seven or eight?
ROUND 2 PRIVATE TALKS
I had some wrong tags.
LOST 4 POINTS FROM 2 WRONG TAGS
What?
TOTAL 8 TAGS
2 WRONG TAGS
[Horseking] I was going to
tag everyone at first,
but I changed my plans in the middle.
I decided to only tag
the people I was sure about
and secure points.
You can tag me.
Please tag me.
AVOIDS SUSPICIOUS PLAYERS
TAGS ONLY THE SURE TARGETS
No.
TOTAL 6 TAGS
0 WRONG TAGS
Three, three.
AND THIRD PLACE YOUN SANGHYUN
Seven, eight, nine.
I was in third place,
but I couldn't relax.
[♪ contemplative music playing]
It's because I was the prime suspect
for being the Seeker.
In fact,
if you don't come in first place,
it's meaningless.
You need to get
an Elimination Immunity Pass
to stay out of the vote.
To me, aside from voting,
I'm still suspicious of him.
I think Sanghyun is the one.
[Jaegyun] Youn Sanghyun...
[Dail] I wonder
what kind of chase they're doing.
[Pani Bottle] The next vote
will mostly likely be against Sanghyun.
He'll be voted out.
[Pani Bottle] They should all suspect him.
Right.
If Sanghyun isn't the Seeker,
I think we're screwed.
It has to be him.
But if it's not Sanghyun,
the Seeker must be thrilled now.
They're not even on anyone's radar.
And everyone's turning on each other.
-It's the best-case scenario.
-[Sujin] It's a great situation.
[Sanghyun] I had to finish in first
and get the Elimination Immunity Pass.
I had to solve
the mystery of the Wolf count.
There's something going on.
When were you a Wolf?
[ZZONE] On Thursday.
Was there anything strange?
-[ZZONE] Strange?
-Yeah.
-The Wolves...
-[ZZONE] The Wolf count is off.
But the Hunter count is right.
Don't you think there are too many Wolves?
There are too many, I did the math.
Starting from Wednesday, it was weird.
There were too many Wolves.
But there are only nine of us.
I knew there were only nine of us.
And each person becomes a Wolf once,
so the total number of Wolves from Monday
to Saturday should add up to nine.
What the heck? Two...
But there were too many Wolves.
So there was a total of 15 Wolves,
and the number of Hunters
was exactly nine.
So the Wolves...
So that's the advantage the Seeker gets.
-[♪ contemplative music playing]
-[Sanghyun] There were 15 Wolves in total.
There was one extra Wolf every day
from Monday to Saturday.
That means there are six extra Wolves.
Maybe it's the Seeker's perk.
The moment I realized that,
I could tell that the Seeker
was up to something.
I believe
it's one of the Seeker's abilities.
There was a Wolf every day.
The Seeker has been a Wolf the whole time.
POSSIBLE SEEKER ABILITY
BEING A WOLF EVERY DAY
Or the Seeker might have picked someone
to become a Wolf
to create confusion.
Maybe each of us had an extra turn
without being aware of it.
Then, everything would add up.
POSSIBLE SEEKER ABILITY
LET SOMEONE ELSE BE A WOLF
There are nine of us,
and there are six extra Wolves.
There are six,
so three players didn't get that chance.
Let's think about why those three
didn't get a chance.
Maybe the order they entered?
It was probably given to those
who were at a disadvantage.
A WOLF PERK FOR THE UNDERDOGS?
If we look at it that way,
-that makes sense.
-[Horseking] Yeah.
I thought the same.
Maybe it's those
with the lowest the funds.
So if this theory is correct,
the first six people
entering the Placement Room
will be assigned as Wolves.
To know for sure,
-[Horseking] last place...
-[Jaegyun] Jieun entered the room first.
Then, we can check if she's a Wolf.
-[Jaegyun] On Monday?
-[Horseking] Yes.
[Jieun] If the Seeker gave the underdogs
the advantage of being Wolves,
maybe we get a Wolf marker by order
in which we enter the Placement Room.
That's the theory that came up.
To know for sure,
Jieun should place her Wolf marker
on any day beside Monday,
tag someone right away,
and check her score.
[Jieun] To see if I got points as a Wolf
or got points as a Dog,
I had to tag someone to check.
If I'm a Wolf,
I'd get three points as a bonus.
SHIN JIEUN
If I'm a Dog,
I'd still get one point.
At the start of Round 2 on Monday,
I'll be the first one to go in,
and we'll confirm if I'm a Wolf or not.
The rest has to be Dogs on Monday.
-[Horseking] Right.
-[Jieun] Yes.
[Jaegyun] Let's promise
not to pick anything else
-and discuss it on Monday.
-Okay.
A TRUCE SO EVERYONE
CAN BE DOGS ON MONDAY
If everyone is a Dog on Monday,
there should be only one Wolf.
Yeah, that's right.
On Monday,
if someone breaks this promise...
-[Jaegyun] It'll be a disaster.
-...it'll be a disaster.
If someone chooses
to be a Hunter or a Wolf,
-everything's ruined.
-[Jaegyun] Exactly.
If that happens,
we'll have to run around like Round 1.
MONDAY
[Junseo] Has everyone agreed to this plan?
[Horseking] In my opinion,
if the Seeker wanted to troll us,
they would do something else here.
[host] Marker placement
for Round 2 is complete.
[alarm blaring]
[host] Monday has begun.
We were right. And no one turned on us.
[gasps] There's no other Wolf now.
There's one Wolf.
[Joonsu] One Wolf. Right.
[Jaegyun] Our theory seems correct.
JIEUN IS THE WOLF?
I think we were right.
[Horseking] Based on our theory,
-she's in last place.
-[Jaegyun] We'll go check.
I might not be a Wolf.
-[Jaegyun] Then, we're wrong.
-Hey, go to the Dealer.
JIEUN TAGS JAEGYUN
They're checking right away.
Jieun tagged him.
STRAIGHT TO THE PLACEMENT ROOM
TO CHECK HER SCORE
I'd like to check my score.
[dealer] Ms. Shin Jieun's
current score is...
JIEUN'S ROUND 1 SCORE WAS -19
Jieun is a Wolf?
Yeah, basically.
If she got one point,
it proves Jieun isn't a Wolf.
NEGATIVE 18 POINTS MEAN DOG,
NEGATIVE 16 POINTS MEAN WOLF
Negative 18 points.
Okay, thank you.
CURRENT SCORE IS -18
Our theory was wrong.
-Really?
-[Jieun] I'm not a Wolf.
-[Jaegyun] She's not a Wolf?
-[Jieun] We got it wrong.
You got just one point?
Yes, I earned one point,
so it's at minus 18.
Then, that's a no.
TAGGING AS A WOLF EARNS 3 POINTS
-Then, she's not a Wolf.
-[Joonsu] She's not.
So, the Seeker had been a Wolf.
-The Seeker was a Wolf.
-[Joonsu] Wow...
THE SEEKER HAS BEEN A WOLF THE WHOLE TIME?
[Horseking] This pretty much settles it.
[Junseo] This must be
one of the Seeker's perks.
The Seeker has way more control
over the game than I thought.
If the Seeker was a Wolf the whole time,
let's stay here together.
The Wolf will try to earn more points.
-But we don't know who the Wolf is.
-[Jieun] The Seeker is...
[Horseking] I suspected Sanghyun
from the beginning,
and that suspicion
is moving closer to being certain.
[Sanghyun] Everyone suspects me.
All of them
suspect me of being the Seeker.
-This is scary.
-We should split up.
-Split up.
-[Sanghyun] You're splitting up?
-[Horseking] Huh?
-We're splitting up?
We have to assume our theory was wrong.
We can't use it any longer.
How will you find him?
[Sanghyun] Things don't add up,
so we go our separate ways?
Fine, whatever.
[Joonsu] We have to run away
since this is Round 2.
There's only one minute left.
I need to run away.
THE PLAYERS FALL INTO PANIC
AFTER THEIR THEORY FALLS APART
[Junseo] I thought this was part
of the Seeker's strategy to confuse us.
[Jimin] I felt like
I I couldn't take action anymore.
[Eunsil] I needed to be
a little more careful.
EVERYONE HAS LEFT
SOMETHING MOVES
After the first round,
I kept thinking about it.
Why is there one extra Wolf?
So when everyone dispersed in Round 2,
I hid right next to the Placement Room.
[alarm blaring]
[host] Tuesday has begun.
Looking back,
when I thought about the Dealer Room
or Placement Room
right from the start at Round 1,
something felt off.
I don't know why,
but something kept bothering me.
I couldn't stop thinking about it.
Something's definitely going on here.
[Jimin] Don't you think
there are too many Wolves?
[Jaegyun] But there are only nine of us.
[ZZONE] The Wolf count is off.
Something's off.
[host] The second Main Match is
"Time Between Dogs and Wolves."
Do wolves usually have
different-colored eyes?
[Jaegyun] It's heterochromia.
Different colored eyes.
[Sanghyun] The Seeker.
Heterochromia.
A Wolf Seeker.
I got it.
[♪ ominous music playing]
Translated by Youji Kim